lockerdome.com 2013-06-06

# Privacy Policy - LockerDome

**Last Updated: May 6, 2013**

This Service and Network are owned and operated by LockerDome, LLC (collectively, "us", "we" or "the Company"). Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using the LockerDome Service located at [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/) ("LockerDome" or "Website"), or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/).

By using or accessing LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you visit LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Website use information collected by us as you interact with our Website.

When you register with LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your country, your gender, and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.

When you enter LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all LockerDome visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/). You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

When you use LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), you may form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, set up events, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

By using LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States and elsewhere where the service is available.

**POLICY ON COLLECTING INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register WITHOUT full parental consent and administration of information within a Parent Account. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information outside of a Parent Account. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from anyone under the age of 13 outside of a Parent Account, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or anyone under the age of 13 outside of a Parent Account, please contact us at [support@lockerdome.com](mailto:support@lockerdome.com).

**USE OF INFORMATION OBTAINED BY LOCKERDOME**

When you register with LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), you create your own profile and privacy settings that is viewable by this Network, as well as by the entire LockerDome community. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by LockerDome that we think you may find valuable.

Profile information is used by us primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the Service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information by your privacy settings. In some cases where your privacy settings permit it (e.g., posting to your Comments), other LockerDome users may be able to supplement your profile. You can delete these comments if you wish.

We may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes of providing relevant and targeted advertisements to our Members.

**SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES**

We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you. For example:

  * We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about LockerDome, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the LockerDome -specified purposes.
  * We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Service or using the LockerDome name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.
  * We let you choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through sponsored accounts or other on-site offers.
  * We may provide services jointly with other companies on [lockerdome.com](http://lockerdome.com/). In doing so we may choose to share Member information with these companies to better provide services that are relevant to our Members.
  * If the ownership of the Website, Service, or individual business units owned by LockerDome, LLC were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

**LINKS**

LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other Websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on the LockerDome Platform and any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/).

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

Advertisements that appear on LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by us and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

To learn or more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising for some companies, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**CHANGING OR REMOVING INFORMATION**

Access and control over most personal information on LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), is readily available through the profile editing tools. LockerDome users may modify or remove their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their LockerDome account may do by sending an email to [support@lockerdome.com](mailto:support@lockerdome.com) and writing their request for deactivation in the email. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of LockerDome, or the members at any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/).

**SECURITY**

LockerDome member accounts, any members at any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), are secured by member-created passwords. We take precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use please contact us at [support@lockerdome.com](mailto:support@lockerdome.com).

**TERMS OF USE, NOTICES AND REVISIONS**

If you choose to visit LockerDome, or any subdomain (i.e. [subdomain.lockerdome.com](http://subdomain.lockerdome.com/)) of [www.lockerdome.com](http://www.lockerdome.com/), your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of, and application of law of the state of Missouri. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's effective date. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
